<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:custom="http://your.custom.namespace.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Five Minute Call Podcast Blogs</title>
    <link>https://www.fmc.show</link>
    <description>All blog posts for FMC.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://rayvox.github.io/fmc/blogs.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<item>
  <title>Ellen Jackson: From Motherhood to 12,000 Performances of Phantom of the Opera</title>
  <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/ellen-jackson</url>
  <image_url>https://d3t3ozftmdmh3i.cloudfront.net/staging/podcast_uploaded_episode/40349131/40349131-1715542980494-cdd8f0835d34d.jpg</image_url>
  <contentSnippet>
In this captivating episode of the Five Minute Call podcast, hosts Oren and Claire sit down with the incredibly talented Ellen Jackson, a veteran of the performing arts world. With a career spanning over three decades, Ellen shares her fascinating journey from her early days in Scottish Opera to he...</contentSnippet>
  <pubDate>2024-05-13T16:00:09.000Z</pubDate>
</item><item>
  <title>Johnny Bishop: &quot;Michael Jackson inspired my journey from Trinidad to the West End&quot;</title>
  <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/johnny-bishop</url>
  <image_url>https://d3t3ozftmdmh3i.cloudfront.net/staging/podcast_uploaded_episode/40349131/40349131-1712769499529-d9badc2901a84.jpg</image_url>
  <contentSnippet>
Johnny Bishop is a talented performer who has graced the stages of London&apos;s West End in productions such as Moulin Rouge!, Hamilton, and The Lion King. From his humble beginnings in Trinidad to his rise as a sought-after performer, Johnny shares his journey of passion, dedication, and the relentles...</contentSnippet>
  <pubDate>2024-04-10T18:43:52.000Z</pubDate>
</item><item>
  <title>Lorna Cobbold: Company &amp; Stage Manager (Cabaret, Les Miserable, Lion King, Mary Poppins)</title>
  <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/lorna-cobbold</url>
  <image_url>https://d3t3ozftmdmh3i.cloudfront.net/staging/podcast_uploaded_episode/40349131/40349131-1711372807300-4de9e9306148a.jpg</image_url>
  <contentSnippet>
In this episode of &quot;The Five Minute Call&quot; podcast, hosts Oren and Claire sit down with Lorna Cobbold, a world-class company manager and stage manager with nearly three decades of experience in the performing arts industry. Lorna shares her incredible journey, from her early days as an Assistant Sta...</contentSnippet>
  <pubDate>2024-03-25T16:03:53.000Z</pubDate>
</item><item>
  <title>Jennifer Whyte: West End Musical Director (Les Mis, Avenue Q, Sunset Boulevard, Phantom, Cabaret)</title>
  <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/jennifer-whyte</url>
  <image_url>https://d3t3ozftmdmh3i.cloudfront.net/staging/podcast_uploaded_episode/40349131/40349131-1710424648639-cc7931cf516c5.jpg</image_url>
  <contentSnippet>
In the latest episode of the Five Minute Call podcast, hosts Oren and Claire dive deep into the fascinating story of Jennifer Whyte, a renowned musical director who has left her mark on numerous acclaimed productions such as Les Misérables, Avenue Q, Sunset Boulevard, The Phantom of the Opera, Para...</contentSnippet>
  <pubDate>2024-03-17T11:01:02.000Z</pubDate>
</item>  </channel>
</rss>