<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:custom="http://your.custom.namespace.com" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Five Minute Call Podcast Blogs</title>
    <link>https://www.fmc.show</link>
    <description>All blog posts for FMC.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://rayvox.github.io/fmc/blogs.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>Johnny Bishop: "Michael Jackson inspired my journey from Trinidad to the West End"</title>
      <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/johnny-bishop</url>
      <author>Oren Boder</author>
      <Description>Johnny Bishop is a talented performer who has graced the stages of London's West End in productions such as Moulin Rouge!, Hamilton, and The Lion King. From his humble beginnings in Trinidad to his rise as a sought-after performer, Johnny shares his journey of passion, dedication, and the relentless pursuit of his dreams. Listeners will be inspired by Johnny's unwavering commitment to his craft and his ability to overcome the challenges faced by young...</Description>
      <dateCreated/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lorna Cobbold: Company &amp; Stage Manager (Cabaret, Les Miserable, Lion King, Mary Poppins)</title>
      <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/lorna-cobbold</url>
      <author>Oren Boder</author>
      <Description>In this episode of "The Five Minute Call" podcast, hosts Oren and Claire sit down with Lorna Cobbold, a world-class company manager and stage manager with nearly three decades of experience in the performing arts industry. Lorna shares her incredible journey, from her early days as an Assistant Stage Manager (ASM) at the Royal Court Theatre to her current role as a highly sought-after Company Stage Manager in London's West End and on Broadway. Througho...</Description>
      <dateCreated/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Whyte: West End Musical Director (Les Mis, Avenue Q, Sunset Boulevard, Phantom, Cabaret)</title>
      <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/jennifer-whyte</url>
      <author>Oren Boder</author>
      <Description>In the latest episode of the Five Minute Call podcast, hosts Oren and Claire dive deep into the fascinating story of Jennifer Whyte, a renowned musical director who has left her mark on numerous acclaimed productions such as Les Misérables, Avenue Q, Sunset Boulevard, The Phantom of the Opera, Parade, and Cabaret.  Throughout the episode, Jennifer emphasises the importance of adaptability in the world of musical theatre, as well as the significance of...</Description>
      <dateCreated/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kris Hedges-Manuel - Embracing the Ensemble / Starting a successful school during lockdown</title>
      <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/kris-hedges-manuel</url>
      <author>Oren Boder</author>
      <Description>In the latest episode of The 5 Minute Call podcast, hosts Claire and Oren sit down with West End veteran Kris Manuel for a captivating conversation about his remarkable journey in the world of theatre. With a career spanning over two decades, Kris has graced the stages of some of the most iconic shows, including Starlight Express, Billy Elliot, Matilda the Musical, and Phantom of the Opera. Throughout the episode, Kris shares his experiences, challenge...</Description>
      <dateCreated/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexia Khadime - Grammy Nominated Actress | Prince of Egypt / Les Miserable / Wicked / Lion King</title>
      <url>https://www.rayvox.co.uk/blogs/five-minute-call-podcast/alexia-khadime</url>
      <author>Oren Boder</author>
      <Description>In this episode of the Five Minute Call podcast, hosts Oren and Claire sit down with Alexia Khadime, a Grammy Nominated actress known for her roles in Wicked (Elphaba), the Prince of Egypt (Miriam), The Lion King (Nala), Les Misérables (Eponine), and The Book of Mormon (Nabulungi). Alexia shares her incredible journey from a young girl who loved to sing to becoming a seasoned professional in the musical theatre industry. She discusses the importance of...</Description>
      <dateCreated/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>